So, I am here to tell you all that I am very proud to announce that Smart, Funny & Black will be doing two free shows in Nashville, Tennessee on June 17th in partnership with the National Museum of African American Music.
When I say free shows, I am gifting these shows to the city of Nashville.
I'm footing the bill and we're going to have all of the trappings.
My band will be there.
The slideshow will be there.
I will be there.
And we are going to be doing two free shows at the National Museum of African American Music on June 17th in partnership with their Juneteenth activities.
I'm doing this because when I looked at what's going on in Tennessee and we saw what happened with the Tennessee 3, I just felt like, you know what, these people, they need a break.
And I just keep feeling like I'm seeing all of these right-wing places and these people gathering and they be supporting each other in their foolishness.
We need to be supporting each other in our dopeness, in our greatness.
In our innovation, we need to be supporting each other in our healing, in our revitalization, fighting all the time wears you out.
Where can we go to get built back up?
You can go to Smart, Funny & Black.
I ask that everyone only get two tickets.
Sign up at AmandaSeals.com and get your tickets to Smart, Funny & Black June 17th at the National Museum of African American Music in Nashville, Tennessee.
See y'all there.
Smart, Funny & Black!